<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Findings on UVA Biocomplexity Institute</title>
    <link>/findings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Findings on UVA Biocomplexity Institute</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/findings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Results Section One</title>
      <link>/findings/results-section-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/findings/results-section-one/</guid>
      <description>/* this chunnk of code centers all of the headings */ h1, h2, h3 { text-align: center; }  Main Findings Correctional Education Study Findings: Even small levels of improvement can increase an individual&#39;s ability to function in the community. Page County has low infrastructure which is a barrier to increasing education via: remote work, education and mental health care
   Grants Awarded to Page County: Rural Health Opioid Program</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Results Section Two</title>
      <link>/findings/results-section-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/findings/results-section-two/</guid>
      <description> Main Findings Isochrone Mapping  Spatial Variables       Conclusion and Policy Implications [Here you could highlight the main takeaways and the potential policy implications of your findings.]
 References [List your references here using APA format (or at least standardize all of the references using the same format).]
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Results Section Three</title>
      <link>/findings/results-section-three/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/findings/results-section-three/</guid>
      <description>[Here you will describe the data discoversy process, the data used, and the methods employed for this single page. Since you already have a Project Overview and Data &amp;amp; Methods tabs, you probably want to keep this first paragraph fairly short and use the rest of the document to walk your readers through your analyses.]
Main Findings Factor Analysis  Composite Vulnerability Score  Conclusion and Policy Implications [Here you could highlight the main takeaways and the potential policy implications of your findings.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>